<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dog Breeds</string>

    <string name="day_1">Day 1</string>
    <string name="day_2">Day 2</string>
    <string name="day_3">Day 3</string>
    <string name="day_4">Day 4</string>
    <string name="day_5">Day 5</string>
    <string name="day_6">Day 6</string>
    <string name="day_7">Day 7</string>
    <string name="day_8">Day 8</string>
    <string name="day_9">Day 9</string>
    <string name="day_10">Day 10</string>
    <string name="day_11">Day 11</string>
    <string name="day_12">Day 12</string>
    <string name="day_13">Day 13</string>
    <string name="day_14">Day 14</string>
    <string name="day_15">Day 15</string>
    <string name="day_16">Day 16</string>
    <string name="day_17">Day 17</string>
    <string name="day_18">Day 18</string>
    <string name="day_19">Day 19</string>
    <string name="day_20">Day 20</string>
    <string name="day_21">Day 21</string>
    <string name="day_22">Day 22</string>
    <string name="day_23">Day 23</string>
    <string name="day_24">Day 24</string>
    <string name="day_25">Day 25</string>
    <string name="day_26">Day 26</string>
    <string name="day_27">Day 27</string>
    <string name="day_28">Day 28</string>
    <string name="day_29">Day 29</string>
    <string name="day_30">Day 30</string>

    <string name="breed_1">Labrador Retriever</string>
    <string name="breed_2">German Wirehaired Pointer</string>
    <string name="breed_3">Cavalier King Charles Spaniel</string>
    <string name="breed_4">Border Collie</string>
    <string name="breed_5">Samoyed</string>
    <string name="breed_6">Beagle</string>
    <string name="breed_7">Dalmatian</string>
    <string name="breed_8">Lowchen</string>
    <string name="breed_9">French Bulldog</string>
    <string name="breed_10">Akita</string>
    <string name="breed_11">Bichon Frise</string>
    <string name="breed_12">Tibetan mastiff</string>
    <string name="breed_13">Golden Retriever</string>
    <string name="breed_14">Pharaoh Hound</string>
    <string name="breed_15">American Pit Bull terrier</string>
    <string name="breed_16">Rottweiler</string>
    <string name="breed_17">Dachshund</string>
    <string name="breed_18">English Setter</string>
    <string name="breed_19">Great Dane</string>
    <string name="breed_20">Irish Wolfhound</string>
    <string name="breed_21">Pug</string>
    <string name="breed_22">Papillon</string>
    <string name="breed_23">Miniature poodle</string>
    <string name="breed_24">English Bulldog</string>
    <string name="breed_25">Yorkshire terrier</string>
    <string name="breed_26">Boxer</string>
    <string name="breed_27">Siberian Husky</string>
    <string name="breed_28">American Foxhound</string>
    <string name="breed_29">Doberman Pinscher</string>
    <string name="breed_30">Harrier</string>

    <string name="summary_1">Labs are friendly, outgoing, and high-spirited companions </string>
    <string name="summary_2">German Pointers are very intelligent, responsive, and eager to please</string>
    <string name="summary_3">The Cavalier is a sweet, gentle, and affectionate breed</string>
    <string name="summary_4">Border Collies are highly intelligent and highly trainable</string>
    <string name="summary_5">These are smart, social, mischievous dogs who demand love and attention</string>
    <string name="summary_6">Beagles are active, energetic dogs who need at least an hour of exercise every day</string>
    <string name="summary_7">The dignified Dalmatian, dogdom\'s citizen of the world, is famed for his spotted coat and unique job description.</string>
    <string name="summary_8">Lowchen is a European breed known for its petite frame, mane-like fur, and playful attitudes</string>
    <string name="summary_9">French Bulldogs are quirky, playful and full of energy</string>
    <string name="summary_10">Akitas are quiet, fastidious dogs. Wary of strangers and often intolerant of other animals</string>
    <string name="summary_11">Bichons have a reputation for being difficult to housebreak. In every other respect, however, they are very easy to train.</string>
    <string name="summary_12">Watchful, aloof, imposing, and intimidating</string>
    <string name="summary_13">Golden retrievers are playful, yet gentle with children, and they tend to get along well with other pets and strangers.</string>
    <string name="summary_14">The pharaoh hound is calm, quiet and clean, content to stretch out on your best sofa and sleep as long as you have given him a daily run or romp.</string>
    <string name="summary_15">Pit bulls were bred to be courageous and game, to continue whatever they are doing in the face of adversity. These qualities make them stubborn, tenacious and fearless. As with any large dog, pit bulls should be supervised when with children.</string>
    <string name="summary_16">Rottweilers can be service dogs, therapy dogs, obedience competitors, guide dogs, customs inspectors, drafting and carting dogs, and of course, devoted companions.</string>
    <string name="summary_17">Despite their size, Dachshunds are known for their courageous nature and will take on animals much larger than themselves</string>
    <string name="summary_18">English Setters are elegant but solid dogs of beauty and charm. </string>
    <string name="summary_19">Great Danes are sociable, friendly, and eager to please, and they respond well to firm, consistent training methods.</string>
    <string name="summary_20">Irish wolfhounds have a heart as big as the rest of them. They are gentle, noble, sensitive and easygoing. Despite the fact that they can run at great speed.</string>
    <string name="summary_21">The Pug has been bred to be a companion and a pleasure to his owners. He has an even and stable temperament, great charm, and an outgoing, loving disposition.</string>
    <string name="summary_22">The Papillon is happy, alert, and friendly. He should never be shy or aggressive. </string>
    <string name="summary_23">Miniature poodles are smart, active, and playful. They love to romp and play nearly non-stop as puppies and young dogs</string>
    <string name="summary_24">English bulldogs have a sweet disposition, are predictable, dependable and excellent with children and need only moderate exercise.</string>
    <string name="summary_25">Tenacious, feisty, brave, and sometimes bossy, the Yorkie exhibits all the traits of a true terrier.</string>
    <string name="summary_26">Boxers are stocky, muscular and powerful. Their jaw is undershot and the muzzle blunt.</string>
    <string name="summary_27">Siberian huskies are probably best-known for their incredible sled-pulling skills, but these doggies are not all business! Indeed, they make excellent working dogs, as they were bred originally to help the Chukchi people of Siberia hunt more efficiently. But they\'re sweet, friendly, and loyal cuddle bugs, too</string>
    <string name="summary_28">The breed is famously easygoing, mild, and good-natured, especially those raised in a home.</string>
    <string name="summary_29">A Doberman Pinscher is extremely loyal to his family. A Doberman Pinscher is very sweet and affectionate with the family children, provided he has been raised with them. He views the kids as the puppies in the pack. A Doberman Pinscher is a fantastic guard dog that will be the ultimate protector for your kids.</string>
    <string name="summary_30">Harriers are loving and amiable but also tend to have an independent nature, and they can be stubborn.</string>
</resources>